Ayan has caught his royal brother
staring blankly in the study several times.
But after Sister Xiaoyue came,
royal brother started smiling.
Is he really that lonely?
If you are worried about him,
go and check on him.
He does seem a bit different today.
I'll go check on him.
Wait.
Are you really leaving?
Damn data man.
You want to drink, too.
I will satisfy you.
How is it?
Is it good?
No.
Not good.
What's wrong with you?
Why are your eyes so red?
Why did you go to see Jingyuan?
Ah.
What?
Speak.
Let go.
I am a human being, not your pet cat or dog.
Why do you care who I went to see?
Si Xingxuan.
His eyes are red,
and he looks violent.
He must be sick.
I need to get a royal physician to take a look at him.
I have studied medicine for fifty years.
I have never seen a pulse like Your Majesty's before.
Your Majesty goes mad and turns on everyone,
but it doesn't seem like an illness.
What's wrong?
Get out.
Speak.
Let go of me.
It's not an illness.
It's poison.
Report.
Your Majesty, I intercepted the Grand Princess's carriage
that was transferring Consort Rong's sister.
I don't know what kind of torture she suffered.
Talking about witchcraft and black magic.
Could there be...
strange places in Aunt's mansion?
Like an isolated little house,
strange noises,
or a dungeon?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Last time I saw a little rabbit,
and it hopped and hopped,
then suddenly disappeared.
Suddenly disappeared?
Then Aunt said
not to enter that hole,
because she said there's a monster inside.
Then do you remember
where that monster is?
Are you going?
Okay.